<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://filelint.com</loc>
    <changefreq>weekly</changefreq>
    <priority>1.0</priority>
  </url>
</urlset>
```

---

### 3. Launch Posts (This Week — Free, High Impact)

These drive the first wave of real users:

**Reddit posts — do all three:**
- `r/webdev` — "I built a free file validator that auto-fixes broken JSON, YAML, CSV and more"
- `r/programming` — same post
- `r/devtools` — same post

**Template:**
```
I got tired of pasting internal configs into random online validators 
so I built FileLint — a free tool that validates and auto-fixes 
JSON, YAML, CSV, Python, SQL, HTML and more.

Drop any file → instant error detection → one-click auto-fix
Privacy-first: files are never stored.

https://filelint.com

Would love feedback!
```

**HackerNews Show HN:**
```
Show HN: FileLint – drag-and-drop file validator with auto-fix (filelint.com)
```

**Product Hunt:**
- Schedule a launch for a Tuesday or Wednesday morning
- These are the highest traffic days

---

### 4. Content Pages (Week 2–4 — Biggest Long-Term Win)

Create dedicated pages for each file type. Each page targets a high-volume search term and embeds the tool. This is how you get consistent organic traffic for years.

Add these routes to your React app:

| Page | Target Keyword | Monthly Searches |
|---|---|---|
| `/json-validator` | json validator online | 110K |
| `/yaml-validator` | yaml validator | 40K |
| `/csv-validator` | csv validator online | 12K |
| `/json-formatter` | json formatter | 180K |
| `/sql-formatter` | sql formatter online | 25K |
| `/python-syntax-checker` | python syntax checker | 8K |

Each page needs:
- A unique `<title>` and `<meta description>`
- A short paragraph explaining what the validator does
- The tool embedded and pre-filtered to that file type
- A simple FAQ section (Google loves these for featured snippets)

---

### 5. Privacy Angle — Add To Your UI

Your biggest differentiator over JSONLint, YAMLlint etc. is privacy. Add this line to the drop zone subtitle:
```
Files are never stored or transmitted to third parties.
Validated locally on our server and immediately deleted.